<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>

<kickstart>

<description>
	hpcdev-003 specific configuration common to all nodes.
</description>

<copyright>
	Copyright (c) 2000 - 2017 The Regents of the University of California.
	All rights reserved. Rocks(r) v6.2/v7.0 www.rocksclusters.org
</copyright>

<package>dstat</package>
<package>iotop</package>
<package>libaio-devel</package>
<package>perf</package>
<package>strace</package>
<package>sysstat</package>
<package>tree</package>
<package>vim-minimal</package>

<post>

<file name="/etc/motd" mode="append">
<![CDATA[
                                                                              
                                   WELCOME TO                                 
             __                   __                ____  ____ _____          
            / /_  ____  _________/ /__ _   __      / __ \/ __ \__  /          
           / __ \/ __ \/ ___/ __  / _ \ | / /_____/ / / / / / //_ <           
          / / / / /_/ / /__/ /_/ /  __/ |/ /_____/ /_/ / /_/ /__/ /           
         /_/ /_/ .___/\___/\__,_/\___/|___/      \____/\____/____/            
              /_/                                                             
                                                                              
]]>
</file>


<!-- Implement SDSC Security SSH Login Banner -->
<file name="/etc/sshd_banner" mode="create" perms="0644">
<![CDATA[

+------------------------------------------------------------------------------+
|                                   WARNING                                    |
+------------------------------------------------------------------------------+
| This computer system, which is maintained & administered by UCSD Staff, is   |
| for authorized use only. Users have no expectation of privacy in any         |
| materials they place or view on this system.                                 |
|                                                                              |
| This system is for authorized use only. It is not designed or intended to    |
| host or process sensitive data including but not limited to Personal or      |
| Protected Health Information (PHI) as defined by the Health Insurance        |
| Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), Personally Identifiable          |
| Information (PII), Federally protected information as defined by the Federal |
| Information Security Management Act (FISMA), or information regulated by the |
| International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR). If you require a system to |
| process such information, please contact the San Diego Supercomputer Center  |
| (SDSC) Security Department.                                                  |
|                                                                              |
| SDSC complies with state and federal law regarding certain legally protected |
| confidential information, but makes no representation that any other uses of |
| this system will be private or confidential. By continuing to use this       |
| system you indicate your awareness of and consent to these terms and         |
| conditions of use.                                                           |
|                                                                              |
| LOG OFF IMMEDIATELY if you do not agree to the conditions stated in this     |
| warning.                                                                     |
+------------------------------------------------------------------------------+

]]>
</file>

/usr/bin/sed 's,^#Banner none$,Banner /etc/sshd_banner,' /etc/ssh/sshd_config

</post>

</kickstart>
